<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>politiwatch on R. Miles McCain</title>
    <link>https://miles.land/tags/politiwatch/</link>
    <description>Recent content in politiwatch on R. Miles McCain</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2019 21:49:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://miles.land/tags/politiwatch/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>PrivacySpy</title>
      <link>https://miles.land/portfolio/privacyspy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2019 21:49:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/portfolio/privacyspy/</guid>
      <description>PrivacySpy rates companies&amp;rsquo; privacy policies on a ten-point scale, so you can easily understand how your data is being treated online. I started PrivacySpy with Igor Barakaiev in the summer of 2019.
You can view the site at PrivacySpy.org, install the browser extension here, and view the source code on GitHub.
The New York Times named PrivacySpy a &amp;ldquo;Tip of the Week&amp;rdquo; as part of its Privacy Project, writing:
 Privacy policies are long, boring and extremely consequential documents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WhoAreMyRepresentatives</title>
      <link>https://miles.land/portfolio/whoaremyrepresentatives/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2016 21:49:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/portfolio/whoaremyrepresentatives/</guid>
      <description>WhoAreMyRepresentatives.org (WAMR) is a simple tool to look up the government representatives for any U.S. address. It pulls its information from the Google Civics API and the OpenSecrets API.
 Used more than 1 million times and maintains steady traffic. Displayed in the top spot of Hacker News for over nine hours. Featured on ProductHunt. Hit the front page of Reddit (5k+ upvotes). Received an (informal) invitation to visit Google. Shared by Dave Lee, Colin Wright, HANA, Mike Elgan, and others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PolitiTweet</title>
      <link>https://miles.land/portfolio/polititweet/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2016 17:14:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/portfolio/polititweet/</guid>
      <description>PolitiTweet preserves the public record by archiving the tweets of major public figures and prominently displaying those that have been deleted.
View the site at polititweet.org or read the source code on GitHub.
Media Coverage Nightly News with Lester Holt: &amp;ldquo;Wide Range of Celebrities Accidentally Tweeted Russian Propaganda During 2016 Election&amp;rdquo; &amp;mdash; &amp;ldquo;Famous Twitter users with big followers, from Ivanka Trump to comedians Trevor Noah and Sarah Silverman, inadvertently shared tweets that came from accounts linked to Russia, according to social media tracker PolitiTweet.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>