<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>technical on R. Miles McCain</title>
    <link>https://miles.land/tags/technical/</link>
    <description>Recent content in technical on R. Miles McCain</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2020 22:10:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://miles.land/tags/technical/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Open source development</title>
      <link>https://miles.land/portfolio/open-source/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2013 14:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/portfolio/open-source/</guid>
      <description>Most of the software I write is open source, and some people have found this software helpful: collectively, my repositories have over 1,000 &amp;ldquo;stars&amp;rdquo; on GitHub. In maintaining and contributing to these projects, I&amp;rsquo;ve learned about effective community building, communication, advertising, and documentation.
Here are some of the open source projects I maintain:
 Shynet a17t PrivacySpy (with Igor Barakaiev) WhyPrivacyMatters LibreNews IEQL  I also make an effort to contribute to other open source projects as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shynet had a security issue because I misunderstood CORS</title>
      <link>https://miles.land/errata/shynet-had-a-security-issue-because-i-misunderstood-cors/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2020 22:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/errata/shynet-had-a-security-issue-because-i-misunderstood-cors/</guid>
      <description>When I built Shynet, my self-hosted analytics tool, one of my top priorities was making sure it didn’t require visitors to have JavaScript enabled. While Shynet will try to log visits using a JavaScript tracker, it will fall back to a 1x1 transparent tracking pixel if JavaScript isn’t enabled. Here is the Shynet tracking code for this site, for example:
&amp;lt;noscript&amp;gt; &amp;lt;img src=&amp;#34;https://shynet.rmrm.io/ingress/aa93dbb3-7d36-4de1-8642-5074c7e33c92/pixel.gif&amp;#34;&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/noscript&amp;gt; &amp;lt;script src=&amp;#34;https://shynet.rmrm.io/ingress/aa93dbb3-7d36-4de1-8642-5074c7e33c92/script.js&amp;#34;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/script&amp;gt; Like any well-designed web system, Shynet appropriately sets CORS headers on these resources to ensure that its resources are only accessible from the intended domains—in this case, miles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frustrated? It&#39;s not you, it&#39;s Rust</title>
      <link>https://miles.land/cool/frustrated-its-not-you-its-rust/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2020 22:03:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/cool/frustrated-its-not-you-its-rust/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sharing music painlessly</title>
      <link>https://miles.land/posts/music-post-generator/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 15:00:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/posts/music-post-generator/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve always struggled with sharing music. I listen to a lot of it&amp;mdash;sometimes more than eight hours per day&amp;mdash;but for me, music has never been social. I can count on one hand the number of playlists I&amp;rsquo;ve shared with other people, for example, and I usually don&amp;rsquo;t volunteer to be the DJ when I&amp;rsquo;m with friends.
I don&amp;rsquo;t think there&amp;rsquo;s any single cause for my hesitance to share music; I think it&amp;rsquo;s a combination of 1) music services being incompatible with one another, 2) rarely being in situations with friends where me playing music out loud is appropriate, and 3) some degree of insecurity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I thought it’d be a good idea to establish scopes at parse time</title>
      <link>https://miles.land/errata/parse-time-scopes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2020 16:12:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/errata/parse-time-scopes/</guid>
      <description>Over the past week or so, I’ve been working on building my own simple interpreted programming language. My goal is to learn about language design, Lisp, and systems programming—all while building a language that is fun to use (and maybe, just maybe, one day I&amp;rsquo;ll find it useful for something).
Even though the project has gone well so far (mostly thanks to the safety guarantees of the Rust programming language), I also made a lot of mistakes as I implemented the first version of the interpreter, and I&amp;rsquo;m sure I&amp;rsquo;ll make many more over the course of the project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happens when you update your DNS?</title>
      <link>https://miles.land/cool/updating-dns-jvns/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 17:22:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/cool/updating-dns-jvns/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I accidentally broke one of my biggest sites because I used a CDN</title>
      <link>https://miles.land/errata/used-a-cdn-wamr/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 16:23:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/errata/used-a-cdn-wamr/</guid>
      <description>I recently redesigned WhoAreMyRepresentatives with help from some Politiwatch volunteers. It&amp;rsquo;s just a simple flask app, and setting up some kind of asset pipeline for the CSS felt like overkill, so I imported a17t (my CSS library) from a CDN.
All was well until I released a new version of a17t a few days ago. (You can probably see where this is going.) Emails started to roll in about the site &amp;ldquo;being broken,&amp;rdquo; but because there weren&amp;rsquo;t that many reports and none of my uptime checks were failing, I assumed these were isolated incidents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dissecting &#34;Hello World&#34; in Java</title>
      <link>https://miles.land/posts/mcip-hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2020 17:53:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/posts/mcip-hello-world/</guid>
      <description>Note: this post is intended to formalize intuitions about Java for students in my AP CS course. This isn&amp;rsquo;t supposed to be a &amp;ldquo;Hello World&amp;rdquo; tutorial! You&amp;rsquo;ll need some existing experience with Java to find this useful.
 Let&amp;rsquo;s write a very simple Java program that prints Hello, world! to the console. This is just about the simplest program imaginable, and you should already feel comfortable with many of these concepts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fundamental concepts of programming</title>
      <link>https://miles.land/posts/mcip-programming-fundamentals/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2020 17:50:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/posts/mcip-programming-fundamentals/</guid>
      <description>Note: this short post is intended to be a brief introduction to the idea of programming. It&amp;rsquo;s written for students in my AP CS course, but I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to share it with the world as well.
 A computer program is a list of instructions that a computer can execute. Despite being foundational to the modern world, computers themselves are pretty stupid—so these instructions are explicit and simple. A single instruction might ask for something like add 1 and 2 together or print &amp;quot;Hello, world&amp;quot;.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>