<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hey, I&#39;m Miles. on R. Miles McCain</title>
    <link>https://miles.land/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hey, I&#39;m Miles. on R. Miles McCain</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 16:13:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://miles.land/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Stanford University</title>
      <link>https://miles.land/portfolio/stanford/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 02:41:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/portfolio/stanford/</guid>
      <description>Starting in September 2020, I&amp;rsquo;ll be an undergraduate at Stanford. Zoom school! I&amp;rsquo;m just starting, so there&amp;rsquo;s nothing for me to put here yet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PrivacySpy</title>
      <link>https://miles.land/portfolio/privacyspy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2019 21:49:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/portfolio/privacyspy/</guid>
      <description>PrivacySpy rates companies&amp;rsquo; privacy policies on a ten-point scale, so you can easily understand how your data is being treated online. I started PrivacySpy with Igor Barakaiev in the summer of 2019.
You can view the site at PrivacySpy.org, install the browser extension here, and view the source code on GitHub.
The New York Times named PrivacySpy a &amp;ldquo;Tip of the Week&amp;rdquo; as part of its Privacy Project, writing:
 Privacy policies are long, boring and extremely consequential documents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Synthetic Disinformation</title>
      <link>https://miles.land/portfolio/synthetic-disinformation-kreps/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2019 22:55:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/portfolio/synthetic-disinformation-kreps/</guid>
      <description>In this multi-part research project, Dr. Sarah Kreps and I studied how synthetic (AI-generated) disinformation can deceive the public and masquerade as reliable, human-written news.
 Wrote &amp;ldquo;All The News That&amp;rsquo;s Fit to Fabricate: A Study of Synthetic Disinformation&amp;rdquo; with Dr. Kreps and Miles Brundage (forthcoming in the Journal of Experimental Political Science). Co-authored &amp;ldquo;Not Your Father&amp;rsquo;s Bots&amp;rdquo; in Foreign Affairs with Dr. Kreps. Co-authored &amp;ldquo;Taking GPT-2 head-to-head with the New York Times&amp;rdquo; in Brookings&amp;rsquo; TechStream with Dr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Politiwatch</title>
      <link>https://miles.land/portfolio/politiwatch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/portfolio/politiwatch/</guid>
      <description>Politiwatch is a non-profit that technology to promote political accountability, digital rights, and social awareness. I founded Politiwatch as a way to distance myself from some of my more controversial projects. (They weren&amp;rsquo;t that controversial, but I didn&amp;rsquo;t feel comfortable putting my name on them.)
If you find the work I do as Politiwatch impactful, please consider donating.
Politiwatch&amp;rsquo;s sponsors include Google (via their Google for Nonprofits program), Microsoft (though their nonprofit grants program), ProtonMail, and DigitalOcean.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shynet</title>
      <link>https://miles.land/portfolio/shynet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2020 20:55:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/portfolio/shynet/</guid>
      <description>Shynet is a modern, privacy-friendly, and detailed web analytics tool that works without cookies or JS. It&amp;rsquo;s one of my most successful open source projects. Check out the source code and installation instructions on GitHub.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recurse Center</title>
      <link>https://miles.land/portfolio/recurse/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 02:54:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/portfolio/recurse/</guid>
      <description>I was a member of the Recurse Center&amp;rsquo;s Spring 1 2020 batch; like all Recursers, I never graduated.
The Recurse Center&amp;mdash;colloquially known as RC&amp;mdash;is a self-directed academic retreat centered around programming (but certainly not limited to it). Everyone I met at RC was smart, nice, and thoughtful; I believe RC is one of the best communities in the world. It&amp;rsquo;s completely free to attend, so if you&amp;rsquo;re interested, please apply.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Censorship</title>
      <link>https://miles.land/portfolio/chinese-censorship-ip/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 02:04:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/portfolio/chinese-censorship-ip/</guid>
      <description>In this independent research project, Jeffrey Shen and I created CensorScout and the Weibo Censorship Dashboard, two pilot applications that make several steps toward increased transparency into censorship on Weibo and provide valuable&amp;mdash;albeit limited&amp;mdash;information regarding the state of Chinese Internet censorship.
 Published paper for open access on SSRN, made daily top-tens in several sections and top 10% of authors by downloads in the year following. Completed as part of Digital Propaganda &amp;amp; Censorship, an Independent Project at Phillips Academy under the mentorship of John Palfrey, Michael Barker, and Malgorzata Stergios.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Programming</title>
      <link>https://miles.land/portfolio/programming/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jul 2012 04:48:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/portfolio/programming/</guid>
      <description>I love computing; I enjoy building systems, as well as just programming for programming&amp;rsquo;s sake. (The Joy of Computing!)
I am experienced with Python, Rust, Java, and Haskell, as well as the typical assortment web technologies (HTML, JavaScript, CSS, React, Vue, Svelte, and Angular). I&amp;rsquo;m also comfortable using Docker, Kubernetes, Git, Linux, and other systems.
I have some experience with cryptography and the network stack.
For more information about my programming background, check out my GitHub profile.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Phillips Academy Andover</title>
      <link>https://miles.land/portfolio/andover/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2019 02:32:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/portfolio/andover/</guid>
      <description>I went to Andover for 9th through 12th grade. I was lucky to be able to do several independent projects in my senior year on digital propaganda, censorship, cybersecurity, and surveillance.
Awards  Aurelian Honor Society Award (for character, scholarship, and leadership) Cum Laude Society (for high marks) Webster Prize, 10th grade (for excellence in the social sciences) David G. Wood Fellowship, 10th grade (for excellence in writing) Winfield M. Sides Prize, 11th grade (for excellence in computer science) Scoville Award, 11th grade (for an outstanding original paper or project) Top Score in Physics 400 prize exam, 10th grade  Athletics  Varsity Rowing, 1st boat (11th grade) Wrestling (former)  Leadership Positions  Techmasters (co-president) Computer Science Club (co-president) GSA (gender &amp;amp; sexuality alliance; co-president) Proctor (Flagg House) Writing Center (Work Duty)  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>News Catalyst</title>
      <link>https://miles.land/portfolio/news-catalyst/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/portfolio/news-catalyst/</guid>
      <description>In the fall of 2019, I worked at News Catalyst, building digital tools to empower local news organizations. My work at News Catalyst was supported by the Lenfest Institute.
 Created OpenAlerts, a fully-featured and open source breaking news distribution system intended for local newsrooms. (Because OpenAlerts is open source, I remain on the project. See the Projects section.) Worked with Tyler Fisher to create a management system for the American Press Institute&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Table Stakes&amp;rdquo; program.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Russian Disinformation</title>
      <link>https://miles.land/portfolio/russian-disinformation-ip/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2018 02:17:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/portfolio/russian-disinformation-ip/</guid>
      <description>In this independent research project, Jeffrey Shen and I used machine learning and statistics to better understand the Russian disinformation campaign in the 2016 election. We released three blog posts, launched a Twitter bot, an open API, and deployed an interactive machine learning model.
 Published paper for open access on SSRN, made daily top-tens in several sections. Completed as part of Digital Propaganda &amp;amp; Censorship, an Independent Project at Phillips Academy under the mentorship of John Palfrey, Michael Barker, and Malgorzata Stergios.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Look Media</title>
      <link>https://miles.land/portfolio/first-look-media/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jul 2018 04:36:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/portfolio/first-look-media/</guid>
      <description>In the summer of 2018, I worked on the engineering and research teams of First Look Media, the parent company of The Intercept, primarily on authoring an IETF Internet Draft.
 Worked to create an IETF Internet standard (currently a proposed standard) for OpenPGP cryptographic keylist subscriptions, as implemented by Micah Lee&amp;rsquo;s GPGSync. The draft is available here. (I am the primary/first author.) Wrote an engineering blog post about the IETF project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Design</title>
      <link>https://miles.land/portfolio/visual-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2018 18:44:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/portfolio/visual-design/</guid>
      <description>Design is vague. I know. In this context, I&amp;rsquo;m referring to both system design and graphic design.
When I design anything, my top priorities are usability, accessibility, and beauty. With these principles in mind, I built [a17t], my CSS library, and designed several other websites (including the one you&amp;rsquo;re on right now). I also do my best to apply these principles to software design and writing, but that&amp;rsquo;s harder to showcase.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WhoAreMyRepresentatives</title>
      <link>https://miles.land/portfolio/whoaremyrepresentatives/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2016 21:49:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/portfolio/whoaremyrepresentatives/</guid>
      <description>WhoAreMyRepresentatives.org (WAMR) is a simple tool to look up the government representatives for any U.S. address. It pulls its information from the Google Civics API and the OpenSecrets API.
 Used more than 1 million times and maintains steady traffic. Displayed in the top spot of Hacker News for over nine hours. Featured on ProductHunt. Hit the front page of Reddit (5k+ upvotes). Received an (informal) invitation to visit Google. Shared by Dave Lee, Colin Wright, HANA, Mike Elgan, and others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open source development</title>
      <link>https://miles.land/portfolio/open-source/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2013 14:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/portfolio/open-source/</guid>
      <description>Most of the software I write is open source, and some people have found this software helpful: collectively, my repositories have over 1,000 &amp;ldquo;stars&amp;rdquo; on GitHub. In maintaining and contributing to these projects, I&amp;rsquo;ve learned about effective community building, communication, advertising, and documentation.
Here are some of the open source projects I maintain:
 Shynet a17t PrivacySpy (with Igor Barakaiev) WhyPrivacyMatters LibreNews IEQL  I also make an effort to contribute to other open source projects as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More work</title>
      <link>https://miles.land/portfolio/more-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 04:09:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/portfolio/more-work/</guid>
      <description>PACTF I ran PACTF, a global cybersecurity competition with over 1,000 teams and $20,000 in prizes, in 2017 and 2018.
 After being a participant in PACTF 2016, in 2017 I became the project lead (with Alex Reichenbach). Managed sponsors, problem sets, advertising, and digital infrastructure (effectively the entire competition, though I couldn&amp;rsquo;t have done it without help from the project mentors and the rest of the team). Sponsors include Amazon, J.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More research</title>
      <link>https://miles.land/portfolio/more-research/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 02:26:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/portfolio/more-research/</guid>
      <description>Origins of Oversight In this research project, Dr. Sarah Kreps and I processed the entire modern congressional record to study the determinants of foreign policy oversight in Congress. Co-authored with Dr. Kreps. The source code for much of the project is available on GitHub.
 Presented by Dr. Kreps at Yale, Columbia, Cornell, Georgetown, and UC Santa Barbara. Co-authored popular opinion piece in the Washington Post.  Perceptions of Privacy in the COVID-19 Pandemic In this paper, Dr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PolitiTweet</title>
      <link>https://miles.land/portfolio/polititweet/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2016 17:14:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/portfolio/polititweet/</guid>
      <description>PolitiTweet preserves the public record by archiving the tweets of major public figures and prominently displaying those that have been deleted.
View the site at polititweet.org or read the source code on GitHub.
Media Coverage Nightly News with Lester Holt: &amp;ldquo;Wide Range of Celebrities Accidentally Tweeted Russian Propaganda During 2016 Election&amp;rdquo; &amp;mdash; &amp;ldquo;Famous Twitter users with big followers, from Ivanka Trump to comedians Trevor Noah and Sarah Silverman, inadvertently shared tweets that came from accounts linked to Russia, according to social media tracker PolitiTweet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>a17t</title>
      <link>https://miles.land/portfolio/a17t/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2020 21:49:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/portfolio/a17t/</guid>
      <description>a17t is my lightweight open-source atomic design toolkit. It emphasizes customization, modularity, and separation of concerns (to the extent that is practical).
Here&amp;rsquo;s the elevator pitch (from the a17t documentation):
 Some CSS frameworks come prepackaged with all sorts of components that are convenient at first but quickly become limiting. Utility frameworks like Tailwind are awesome, but can be difficult start using on their own.
a17t tries to get the balance right.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More projects</title>
      <link>https://miles.land/portfolio/more-projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 21:50:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/portfolio/more-projects/</guid>
      <description>Here are a few more projects that I&amp;rsquo;ve worked on over the past few years. A number of these projects have been discontinued, so some of the links may be broken!
 WhyPrivacyMatters.org &amp;mdash; a collaborative project to argue for privacy; translated into 16 languages (and counting); over 30 contributors. PowerVoting &amp;mdash; a tool to compare the relative voting power of districts across the United States in federal elections (with Leyla Jacoby).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More skills</title>
      <link>https://miles.land/portfolio/more-skills/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2001 14:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/portfolio/more-skills/</guid>
      <description>Hackathons I love hackathons, whether it&amp;rsquo;s as a participant or—as of recently—a judge. It&amp;rsquo;s hard to replicate the thrill of building.
 HackNEHS 1st place (Fall 2017): won first place in HackNEHS, a &amp;lsquo;hackathon&amp;rsquo; for New England high schools. Blueprint (@ MIT) 2nd place (Winter 2018): won second place in Blueprint, a national annual hackathon hosted at the MIT Media Lab. Hack Exeter (Spring 2019): won the Developer&amp;rsquo;s Award at Hack Exeter, a hackathon hosted at Phillips Exeter Academy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Music you might like (#5)</title>
      <link>https://miles.land/cool/music-september-21-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 16:13:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/cool/music-september-21-2020/</guid>
      <description>Here are 33 songs across 97 genres that I&amp;rsquo;ve been listening to lately. School has started, which means I have less time than I did before. This playlist is a bit shorter than the other ones.
To listen to this playlist on Spotify, click here. Note that song metadata &amp;mdash; the genres, duration, release date, etc. &amp;mdash; is provided by the Spotify API. I don&amp;rsquo;t input this information myself, so it might be wrong!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://miles.land/micros/2020-09-04-18-21-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Sep 2020 18:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/micros/2020-09-04-18-21-21/</guid>
      <description>Finally moved WhyPrivacyMatters.org to more solid infrastructure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Music you might like (#4)</title>
      <link>https://miles.land/cool/music-september-2-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2020 18:13:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/cool/music-september-2-2020/</guid>
      <description>Here are 44 songs across 137 genres that I&amp;rsquo;ve been listening to lately. This playlist is a bit shorter than the others, and pulls a lot from older songs in my library; I haven&amp;rsquo;t spent much time looking for new music lately. Oh well. I hope you find something you like.
To listen to this playlist on Spotify, click here. Note that song metadata &amp;mdash; the genres, duration, release date, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://miles.land/micros/2020-09-02-16-21-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2020 16:11:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/micros/2020-09-02-16-21-21/</guid>
      <description>Not happy with American Express. Due to a glitch, they double billed me this month’s statement balance. I only keep the bare minimum amount of money in my checking account b/c interest is so low, so this caused an overdraft. I call them to see if they will credit me for $25 (the overdraft amount). “The charge didn’t come from us, so we can’t refund it.” Of course the charge didn’t come from you!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://miles.land/micros/2020-08-30-03-51-29/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2020 03:50:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/micros/2020-08-30-03-51-29/</guid>
      <description>“Sleeping with just one pillow is demoralizing.”</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://miles.land/micros/2020-08-26-03-17-56/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 03:16:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/micros/2020-08-26-03-17-56/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Total honesty is what we need and deserve from the President of the United States.&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://miles.land/micros/2020-08-26-03-08-27/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 03:06:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/micros/2020-08-26-03-08-27/</guid>
      <description>A problem: every site and their uncle is now using the app subdomain. Like app.hey.com and app.netlify.com. It&amp;rsquo;s making browser autofill less useful :(</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://miles.land/micros/2020-08-26-01-20-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 01:19:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/micros/2020-08-26-01-20-01/</guid>
      <description>How has it already been 9 days?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://miles.land/micros/2020-08-16-23-29-37/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2020 23:28:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/micros/2020-08-16-23-29-37/</guid>
      <description>Ah—from @ElleArmageddon</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://miles.land/micros/2020-08-16-23-27-39/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2020 23:27:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/micros/2020-08-16-23-27-39/</guid>
      <description>“The apocalypse, but fashion.”</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Music you might like (#3)</title>
      <link>https://miles.land/cool/music-you-might-like-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2020 21:44:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/cool/music-you-might-like-3/</guid>
      <description>Here are 58 songs across 175 genres that I&amp;rsquo;ve been listening to lately. Feels like the end of August&amp;hellip;
To listen to this playlist on Spotify, click here. Note that song metadata &amp;mdash; the genres, duration, release date, etc. &amp;mdash; is provided by the Spotify API. I don&amp;rsquo;t input this information myself, so it might be wrong!
Classic rock  &amp;ldquo;Drume negrita&amp;rdquo; by Ry Cooder, Manuel Galbán  Album Mambo Sinuendo   Genres blues, blues rock, classic rock, country …   Released 2003-01-27   Play Spotify&amp;nbsp;&amp;nearr; YouTube&amp;nbsp;&amp;nearr;      Genreless  &amp;ldquo;Someplace I&amp;#39;m Supposed to Be&amp;rdquo; by Bry Webb  Album Free Will   Genres Unknown   Released 2014-05-20   Play Spotify&amp;nbsp;&amp;nearr; YouTube&amp;nbsp;&amp;nearr;       &amp;ldquo;Song Of A Sinner&amp;rdquo; by Top Drawer  Album Forge Your Own Chains: Heavy Psychedelic Ballads And Dirges 1968-1974   Genres Unknown   Released 2009-11-17   Play Spotify&amp;nbsp;&amp;nearr; YouTube&amp;nbsp;&amp;nearr;       &amp;ldquo;Storm&amp;rdquo; by Rare Silk  Album American Eyes   Genres Unknown   Released 1985   Play Spotify&amp;nbsp;&amp;nearr; YouTube&amp;nbsp;&amp;nearr;       &amp;ldquo;Farther Away&amp;rdquo; by Sam Valdez  Album Farther Away   Genres Unknown   Released 2018-04-20   Play Spotify&amp;nbsp;&amp;nearr; YouTube&amp;nbsp;&amp;nearr;       &amp;ldquo;Dirty Day&amp;rdquo; by Kalbells  Album Ten Flowers   Genres Unknown   Released 2017-07-14   Play Spotify&amp;nbsp;&amp;nearr; YouTube&amp;nbsp;&amp;nearr;      Art rock  &amp;ldquo;The Daily Planet&amp;rdquo; by Mark Hollis  Album Mark Hollis   Genres art rock, melancholia, slowcore   Released 1998-01-01   Play Spotify&amp;nbsp;&amp;nearr; YouTube&amp;nbsp;&amp;nearr;       &amp;ldquo;Om Rama&amp;rdquo; by Alice Coltrane  Album World Spirituality Classics 1:The Ecstatic Music of Alice Coltrane Turiyasangitananda   Genres afrobeat, afrofuturism, afropop, art …   Released 2017-05-05   Play Spotify&amp;nbsp;&amp;nearr; YouTube&amp;nbsp;&amp;nearr;       &amp;ldquo;Burning Down the House&amp;rdquo; by Talking Heads  Album Burning Down the House / I Get Wild / Wild Gravity   Genres art punk, art rock, dance rock, funk …   Released 1983-06-01   Play Spotify&amp;nbsp;&amp;nearr; YouTube&amp;nbsp;&amp;nearr;       &amp;ldquo;Roundabout - 2008 Remaster&amp;rdquo; by Yes  Album Fragile   Genres album rock, art rock, classic rock, hard …   Released 1971-11-26   Play Spotify&amp;nbsp;&amp;nearr; YouTube&amp;nbsp;&amp;nearr;       &amp;ldquo;Love Is Strange - Remastered 2018&amp;rdquo; by Wings  Album Wild Life   Genres album rock, art rock, beatlesque, …   Released 1971-12-07   Play Spotify&amp;nbsp;&amp;nearr; YouTube&amp;nbsp;&amp;nearr;       &amp;ldquo;Golden Years - 2016 Remaster&amp;rdquo; by David Bowie  Album Station to Station (2016 Remaster)   Genres album rock, art rock, classic rock, …   Released 1976-01-23   Play Spotify&amp;nbsp;&amp;nearr; YouTube&amp;nbsp;&amp;nearr;      Freak folk  &amp;ldquo;Sunflower River Blues - Re-Recorded Version&amp;rdquo; by John Fahey  Album Death Chants, Breakdowns And Military Waltzes   Genres american primitive, drone folk, …   Released 1998-01-01   Play Spotify&amp;nbsp;&amp;nearr; YouTube&amp;nbsp;&amp;nearr;       &amp;ldquo;My Lady&amp;#39;s On Fire&amp;rdquo; by Ty Segall  Album Freedom&amp;#39;s Goblin   Genres alternative rock, bay area indie, blues …   Released 2018-01-26   Play Spotify&amp;nbsp;&amp;nearr; YouTube&amp;nbsp;&amp;nearr;       &amp;ldquo;Solid Silk&amp;rdquo; by Stephen Malkmus &amp;amp; The Jicks  Album Sparkle Hard   Genres alternative rock, freak folk, garage …   Released 2018-05-18   Play Spotify&amp;nbsp;&amp;nearr; YouTube&amp;nbsp;&amp;nearr;       &amp;ldquo;Highway Anxiety&amp;rdquo; by William Tyler  Album Modern Country   Genres alternative country, american primitive, …   Released 2016-06-03   Play Spotify&amp;nbsp;&amp;nearr; YouTube&amp;nbsp;&amp;nearr;       &amp;ldquo;To The Workers of The Rock River Valley Region, I have an idea concerning your predicament, and it involves an inner tube, bath mats, and 21 able-bodied men&amp;rdquo; by Sufjan Stevens  Album Illinois   Genres baroque pop, chamber pop, freak folk, …   Released 2005-07-05   Play Spotify&amp;nbsp;&amp;nearr; YouTube&amp;nbsp;&amp;nearr;       &amp;ldquo;No Go (For Louis Macneice)&amp;rdquo; by The Cleaners From Venus  Album Number Thirteen   Genres art rock, c86, chamber pop, dance rock, …   Released 1990   Play Spotify&amp;nbsp;&amp;nearr; YouTube&amp;nbsp;&amp;nearr;      Australian singer-songwriter  &amp;ldquo;Susan&amp;rdquo; by Jack Ladder  Album Blue Poles   Genres australian singer-songwriter   Released 2018-05-04   Play Spotify&amp;nbsp;&amp;nearr; YouTube&amp;nbsp;&amp;nearr;      Indie pop  &amp;ldquo;Your Cover&amp;#39;s Blown&amp;rdquo; by Belle &amp;amp; Sebastian  Album Books   Genres alternative rock, anti-folk, baroque …   Released 2004-06-21   Play Spotify&amp;nbsp;&amp;nearr; YouTube&amp;nbsp;&amp;nearr;       &amp;ldquo;Innerspace&amp;rdquo; by The Apples In Stereo  Album Fun Trick Noisemaker   Genres alternative rock, athens indie, denver …   Released 1995   Play Spotify&amp;nbsp;&amp;nearr; YouTube&amp;nbsp;&amp;nearr;       &amp;ldquo;Come And Play In The Milky Night&amp;rdquo; by Stereolab  Album Cobra And Phases Group Play Voltage In The Milky Night (Expanded Edition)   Genres alternative rock, art pop, art rock, …   Released 1999   Play Spotify&amp;nbsp;&amp;nearr; YouTube&amp;nbsp;&amp;nearr;       &amp;ldquo;Little Woman&amp;rdquo; by Twin Shadow  Album Caer   Genres alternative dance, art pop, chillwave, …   Released 2018-04-27   Play Spotify&amp;nbsp;&amp;nearr; YouTube&amp;nbsp;&amp;nearr;       &amp;ldquo;Congratulations&amp;rdquo; by MGMT  Album Congratulations   Genres alternative dance, indie pop, indie …   Released 2010-04-09   Play Spotify&amp;nbsp;&amp;nearr; YouTube&amp;nbsp;&amp;nearr;       &amp;ldquo;Yoshimi Battles the Pink Robots, Pt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://miles.land/micros/2020-08-16-00-31-55/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2020 00:31:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/micros/2020-08-16-00-31-55/</guid>
      <description>This site is now 63.5kb in Chrome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shynet had a security issue because I misunderstood CORS</title>
      <link>https://miles.land/errata/shynet-had-a-security-issue-because-i-misunderstood-cors/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2020 22:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/errata/shynet-had-a-security-issue-because-i-misunderstood-cors/</guid>
      <description>When I built Shynet, my self-hosted analytics tool, one of my top priorities was making sure it didn’t require visitors to have JavaScript enabled. While Shynet will try to log visits using a JavaScript tracker, it will fall back to a 1x1 transparent tracking pixel if JavaScript isn’t enabled. Here is the Shynet tracking code for this site, for example:
&amp;lt;noscript&amp;gt; &amp;lt;img src=&amp;#34;https://shynet.rmrm.io/ingress/aa93dbb3-7d36-4de1-8642-5074c7e33c92/pixel.gif&amp;#34;&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/noscript&amp;gt; &amp;lt;script src=&amp;#34;https://shynet.rmrm.io/ingress/aa93dbb3-7d36-4de1-8642-5074c7e33c92/script.js&amp;#34;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/script&amp;gt; Like any well-designed web system, Shynet appropriately sets CORS headers on these resources to ensure that its resources are only accessible from the intended domains—in this case, miles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frustrated? It&#39;s not you, it&#39;s Rust</title>
      <link>https://miles.land/cool/frustrated-its-not-you-its-rust/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2020 22:03:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/cool/frustrated-its-not-you-its-rust/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>To the future occupants of my office at the MIT Media Lab</title>
      <link>https://miles.land/cool/to-the-future-occupants-of-my-office-at-the-mit-media-lab/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2020 21:41:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/cool/to-the-future-occupants-of-my-office-at-the-mit-media-lab/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spot the error on the nutrition label...</title>
      <link>https://miles.land/errata/spot-the-error-on-the-nutrition-label/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2020 18:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/errata/spot-the-error-on-the-nutrition-label/</guid>
      <description>I usually only write about my own mistakes, but here I&amp;rsquo;m going to be writing about a mistake I noticed an error on the nutrition label of Quaker Oatmeal Squares cereal. The error is extremely minor (at least as far as I can tell), but it made me think—this label has been printed and seen probably millions of times, and yet this error remains on the box to this day (as of mid-August 2020).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://miles.land/micros/2020-08-08-19-59-09/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Aug 2020 19:58:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/micros/2020-08-08-19-59-09/</guid>
      <description>There is something weird about Azure. It feels like everything is nested behind three layers of Microsoft legacy abstractions. But hey. It&amp;rsquo;s free. (And it&amp;rsquo;s better than AWS!)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Howland will forgery trial</title>
      <link>https://miles.land/cool/howland-trial/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2020 22:35:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/cool/howland-trial/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Yoda of Silicon Valley</title>
      <link>https://miles.land/cool/knuth-nytimes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2020 22:26:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/cool/knuth-nytimes/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Music you might like (#2)</title>
      <link>https://miles.land/cool/music-july-31-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 18:13:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/cool/music-july-31-2020/</guid>
      <description>Here are 69 songs across 172 genres that I&amp;rsquo;ve been listening to lately. This playlist is nearly six hours long, so I hope the genre groupings are helpful in surfacing music you might like. Like MYML #1, this one has no real theme&amp;mdash;it&amp;rsquo;s just songs I like.
To listen to this playlist on Spotify, click here. Note that song metadata &amp;mdash; the genres, duration, release date, etc. &amp;mdash; is provided by the Spotify API.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A College Degree Is No Guarantee of a Good Life</title>
      <link>https://miles.land/cool/college-happy-atlantic/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2020 02:24:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/cool/college-happy-atlantic/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://miles.land/micros/2020-07-30-19-31-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2020 19:29:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/micros/2020-07-30-19-31-16/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft Azure offers $3,500 per year in Azure credits for nonprofits. That&amp;rsquo;s&amp;hellip; the future of Politiwatch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sharing music painlessly</title>
      <link>https://miles.land/posts/music-post-generator/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 15:00:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/posts/music-post-generator/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve always struggled with sharing music. I listen to a lot of it&amp;mdash;sometimes more than eight hours per day&amp;mdash;but for me, music has never been social. I can count on one hand the number of playlists I&amp;rsquo;ve shared with other people, for example, and I usually don&amp;rsquo;t volunteer to be the DJ when I&amp;rsquo;m with friends.
I don&amp;rsquo;t think there&amp;rsquo;s any single cause for my hesitance to share music; I think it&amp;rsquo;s a combination of 1) music services being incompatible with one another, 2) rarely being in situations with friends where me playing music out loud is appropriate, and 3) some degree of insecurity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://miles.land/micros/2020-07-28-05-16-34/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2020 05:16:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/micros/2020-07-28-05-16-34/</guid>
      <description>Anti-tech or ante-tech?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Music you might like (#1)</title>
      <link>https://miles.land/cool/music-july-22-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2020 20:54:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/cool/music-july-22-2020/</guid>
      <description>Here are 39 songs across 117 genres that I&amp;rsquo;ve been listening to lately. There&amp;rsquo;s no common theme to this playlist beyond the fact that it&amp;rsquo;s all songs I enjoy.
To listen to this playlist on Spotify, click here. Note that song metadata &amp;mdash; the genres, duration, release date, etc. &amp;mdash; is provided by the Spotify API. I don&amp;rsquo;t input this information myself, so it might be wrong!
Art rock  &amp;ldquo;Nuclear War&amp;rdquo; by Sun Ra  Album A Fireside Chat with Lucifer   Genres afrobeat, afrofuturism, art rock, …   Released 1982   Play Spotify&amp;nbsp;&amp;nearr; YouTube&amp;nbsp;&amp;nearr;       &amp;ldquo;I&amp;#39;ll Come Running - 2004 Digital Remaster&amp;rdquo; by Brian Eno  Album Another Green World   Genres ambient, art pop, art rock, …   Released 1975-09-01   Play Spotify&amp;nbsp;&amp;nearr; YouTube&amp;nbsp;&amp;nearr;      Gospel soul  &amp;ldquo;Like a Ship&amp;rdquo; by Pastor T.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://miles.land/micros/2020-07-25-22-23-41/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2020 22:23:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/micros/2020-07-25-22-23-41/</guid>
      <description>If you can&amp;rsquo;t get results back after 7+ days, why run a test at all?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I thought it’d be a good idea to establish scopes at parse time</title>
      <link>https://miles.land/errata/parse-time-scopes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2020 16:12:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/errata/parse-time-scopes/</guid>
      <description>Over the past week or so, I’ve been working on building my own simple interpreted programming language. My goal is to learn about language design, Lisp, and systems programming—all while building a language that is fun to use (and maybe, just maybe, one day I&amp;rsquo;ll find it useful for something).
Even though the project has gone well so far (mostly thanks to the safety guarantees of the Rust programming language), I also made a lot of mistakes as I implemented the first version of the interpreter, and I&amp;rsquo;m sure I&amp;rsquo;ll make many more over the course of the project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://miles.land/micros/2020-07-21-21-19-43/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2020 21:19:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/micros/2020-07-21-21-19-43/</guid>
      <description>NB: don&amp;rsquo;t go to the doctor on an empty stomach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://miles.land/micros/2020-07-21-02-11-42/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2020 02:11:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/micros/2020-07-21-02-11-42/</guid>
      <description>(label &amp;lsquo;setq (macro (identifier value) (label identifier ,value))))</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://miles.land/micros/2020-07-16-13-19-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2020 13:18:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/micros/2020-07-16-13-19-30/</guid>
      <description>Some programming conventions, like infix math notation, are too strong to break. But not all. If-statements begone!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://miles.land/micros/2020-07-16-13-18-41/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2020 13:18:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/micros/2020-07-16-13-18-41/</guid>
      <description>The relationship between sugar in coffee and how good it is ISN&amp;rsquo;T linear.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://miles.land/micros/2020-07-15-20-48-55/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 20:48:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/micros/2020-07-15-20-48-55/</guid>
      <description>Can&amp;rsquo;t tell if the glare is from the smudges on my glasses, or from my computer screen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://miles.land/micros/2020-07-14-23-49-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2020 23:49:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/micros/2020-07-14-23-49-21/</guid>
      <description>I might do the programming language&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://miles.land/micros/2020-07-13-18-29-31/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2020 18:28:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/micros/2020-07-13-18-29-31/</guid>
      <description>Took my Russian placement test just now for school. It was multiple choice. I think I did alright, but I don&amp;rsquo;t feel like I could replicate the texts. Could just identify what was right/wrong. Nervous for the fall&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://miles.land/micros/2020-07-13-00-18-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2020 00:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/micros/2020-07-13-00-18-18/</guid>
      <description>Ran double digit miles for the first time today!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://miles.land/micros/2020-07-12-15-25-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2020 15:24:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/micros/2020-07-12-15-25-12/</guid>
      <description>Resisting the urge to attempt creating a programming language. There are other things to do, I tell myself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://miles.land/micros/2020-07-12-15-03-27/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2020 15:02:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/micros/2020-07-12-15-03-27/</guid>
      <description>This drink smells like Play Doh. It’s good.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://miles.land/micros/2020-07-12-04-58-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2020 04:57:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/micros/2020-07-12-04-58-22/</guid>
      <description>I am better than my Spotify listening history, I promise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://miles.land/micros/2020-07-11-21-56-49/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 21:56:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/micros/2020-07-11-21-56-49/</guid>
      <description>Putting on pants without taking off shoes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://miles.land/micros/2020-07-11-20-48-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 20:47:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/micros/2020-07-11-20-48-15/</guid>
      <description>I’m writing this micro from my phone. I hope you aren’t subscribed to this via RSS!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://miles.land/micros/2020-07-11-20-42-56/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 20:42:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/micros/2020-07-11-20-42-56/</guid>
      <description>Netlify CMS is cool. I&amp;rsquo;m sorry about the URL for micros, though.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://miles.land/micros/im-writing-this-micro-from-netlify-cms-will-it-work-who-will-the-commit-show-up-as/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 20:33:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/micros/im-writing-this-micro-from-netlify-cms-will-it-work-who-will-the-commit-show-up-as/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m writing this micro from Netlify CMS. Will it work? Who will the commit show up as?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Couldn&#39;t figure out why my CSS changes weren&#39;t being applied (turns out I was in prod)</title>
      <link>https://miles.land/errata/wasnt-on-localhost/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 19:45:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/errata/wasnt-on-localhost/</guid>
      <description>I know this is a pretty common mistake, but I just spent 20 minutes debugging a CSS issue before I realized that I was loading the &amp;ldquo;production&amp;rdquo; version of the site and not my local development version.
My local development server was being served at https://localhost:1313, but the page I was testing was https://hugo--milesland.netlify.app/. So of course my fixes weren&amp;rsquo;t working &amp;mdash; I wasn&amp;rsquo;t loading the page with the fixes applied!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why a17t is meant to be used with Tailwind CSS</title>
      <link>https://miles.land/posts/a17t-tailwindcss/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 18:09:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/posts/a17t-tailwindcss/</guid>
      <description>I designed a17t to be used in conjunction with Tailwind CSS. I never use a17t without Tailwind, and I never use Tailwind without a17t.
Why? a17t is an atomic design toolkit. It provides around 30 atomic interface elements&amp;mdash;small, &amp;ldquo;indivisible&amp;rdquo; elements like buttons, form inputs, and headers&amp;mdash;and leaves everything else up to you. The elements themselves are deeply customizable, built with accessibility in mind, and don&amp;rsquo;t come with any built-in spacing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You&#39;ve Got Nothing to Lose (Michael Kiwanuka)</title>
      <link>https://miles.land/cool/youve-got-nothing-to-lose-kiwanuka/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 23:32:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/cool/youve-got-nothing-to-lose-kiwanuka/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://miles.land/micros/matcha-in-mind/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 23:28:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/micros/matcha-in-mind/</guid>
      <description>I want this site to be like matcha.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://miles.land/micros/transcribing-no-fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 23:27:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/micros/transcribing-no-fun/</guid>
      <description>Currently moving all the portfolio content from my old site to this one. It sucks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://miles.land/micros/inter-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 04:59:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/micros/inter-again/</guid>
      <description>Inter is such a good font. I tried building this site using Source Sans Pro, but there&amp;rsquo;s something about Inter that makes it fit much better.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Can Our Ballots Be Both Secret and Secure?</title>
      <link>https://miles.land/cool/secure-ballots-crypto/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 01:30:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/cool/secure-ballots-crypto/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Things Unexpectedly Named After People</title>
      <link>https://miles.land/cool/named-after-people/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 01:30:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/cool/named-after-people/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://miles.land/micros/todos-suck/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 17:36:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/micros/todos-suck/</guid>
      <description>Todo lists suck. They do everything I don&amp;rsquo;t want them to do and nothing I want them to do. (Only slight hyperbole here.)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shynet will never be a SaaS</title>
      <link>https://miles.land/posts/shynet-never-sass/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 17:31:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/posts/shynet-never-sass/</guid>
      <description>Ever since I released Shynet, my open source web analytics tool, several people have asked me if I plan to offer some kind of managed version of the service (presumably as some kind of SaaS). While these requests are super exciting and I sympathize with them—not everyone wants to manage their own servers, after all!—it&amp;rsquo;s not something that I&amp;rsquo;m considering. Here&amp;rsquo;s why.
Self-hosting is the point of Shynet When you use a third-party analytics tool—even one with a strict privacy policy—you&amp;rsquo;re handing your visitors&amp;rsquo; data over to another company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://miles.land/micros/deleted-old-micros/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 17:29:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/micros/deleted-old-micros/</guid>
      <description>I deleted all my demo micros. I&amp;rsquo;m writing this one so that the list doesn&amp;rsquo;t look so sparse.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What happens when you update your DNS?</title>
      <link>https://miles.land/cool/updating-dns-jvns/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 17:22:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/cool/updating-dns-jvns/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I accidentally broke one of my biggest sites because I used a CDN</title>
      <link>https://miles.land/errata/used-a-cdn-wamr/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 16:23:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/errata/used-a-cdn-wamr/</guid>
      <description>I recently redesigned WhoAreMyRepresentatives with help from some Politiwatch volunteers. It&amp;rsquo;s just a simple flask app, and setting up some kind of asset pipeline for the CSS felt like overkill, so I imported a17t (my CSS library) from a CDN.
All was well until I released a new version of a17t a few days ago. (You can probably see where this is going.) Emails started to roll in about the site &amp;ldquo;being broken,&amp;rdquo; but because there weren&amp;rsquo;t that many reports and none of my uptime checks were failing, I assumed these were isolated incidents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cooper Hewitt (Typeface)</title>
      <link>https://miles.land/cool/cooper-hewitt/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 17:57:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/cool/cooper-hewitt/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Goodbye, old posts!</title>
      <link>https://miles.land/posts/goodbye-old-posts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2020 15:09:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/posts/goodbye-old-posts/</guid>
      <description>For my new site, I&amp;rsquo;ll be starting fresh with a new blog. I&amp;rsquo;ve written lots of scattered articles over the years, but I&amp;rsquo;m not going to retroactively import them here. I&amp;rsquo;m going to start fresh.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dissecting &#34;Hello World&#34; in Java</title>
      <link>https://miles.land/posts/mcip-hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2020 17:53:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/posts/mcip-hello-world/</guid>
      <description>Note: this post is intended to formalize intuitions about Java for students in my AP CS course. This isn&amp;rsquo;t supposed to be a &amp;ldquo;Hello World&amp;rdquo; tutorial! You&amp;rsquo;ll need some existing experience with Java to find this useful.
 Let&amp;rsquo;s write a very simple Java program that prints Hello, world! to the console. This is just about the simplest program imaginable, and you should already feel comfortable with many of these concepts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fundamental concepts of programming</title>
      <link>https://miles.land/posts/mcip-programming-fundamentals/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2020 17:50:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/posts/mcip-programming-fundamentals/</guid>
      <description>Note: this short post is intended to be a brief introduction to the idea of programming. It&amp;rsquo;s written for students in my AP CS course, but I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to share it with the world as well.
 A computer program is a list of instructions that a computer can execute. Despite being foundational to the modern world, computers themselves are pretty stupid—so these instructions are explicit and simple. A single instruction might ask for something like add 1 and 2 together or print &amp;quot;Hello, world&amp;quot;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://miles.land/micros/first-update-with-very-very-long-name/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2020 17:14:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/micros/first-update-with-very-very-long-name/</guid>
      <description>This is my first micro post. (I haven&amp;rsquo;t released the site yet.)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Letter</title>
      <link>https://miles.land/letter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/letter/</guid>
      <description>Every once in awhile, I&amp;rsquo;ll be so excited about something that I&amp;rsquo;ll want to share it with you, too. This might be a new project, something I&amp;rsquo;ve come across, or (rarely) a new post. I expect to send a letter roughly once a month or less; I certainly won&amp;rsquo;t be crowding up your inbox.
If this is something you&amp;rsquo;re interested in, sign up using the form below. If an email newsletter isn&amp;rsquo;t your style, you can also follow me on Twitter or subscribe via RSS.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>