<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>more on R. Miles McCain</title>
    <link>https://miles.land/tags/more/</link>
    <description>Recent content in more on R. Miles McCain</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 04:09:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://miles.land/tags/more/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>More work</title>
      <link>https://miles.land/portfolio/more-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2020 04:09:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/portfolio/more-work/</guid>
      <description>PACTF I ran PACTF, a global cybersecurity competition with over 1,000 teams and $20,000 in prizes, in 2017 and 2018.
 After being a participant in PACTF 2016, in 2017 I became the project lead (with Alex Reichenbach). Managed sponsors, problem sets, advertising, and digital infrastructure (effectively the entire competition, though I couldn&amp;rsquo;t have done it without help from the project mentors and the rest of the team). Sponsors include Amazon, J.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More research</title>
      <link>https://miles.land/portfolio/more-research/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 02:26:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/portfolio/more-research/</guid>
      <description>Origins of Oversight In this research project, Dr. Sarah Kreps and I processed the entire modern congressional record to study the determinants of foreign policy oversight in Congress. Co-authored with Dr. Kreps. The source code for much of the project is available on GitHub.
 Presented by Dr. Kreps at Yale, Columbia, Cornell, Georgetown, and UC Santa Barbara. Co-authored popular opinion piece in the Washington Post.  Perceptions of Privacy in the COVID-19 Pandemic In this paper, Dr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More projects</title>
      <link>https://miles.land/portfolio/more-projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 21:50:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/portfolio/more-projects/</guid>
      <description>Here are a few more projects that I&amp;rsquo;ve worked on over the past few years. A number of these projects have been discontinued, so some of the links may be broken!
 WhyPrivacyMatters.org &amp;mdash; a collaborative project to argue for privacy; translated into 16 languages (and counting); over 30 contributors. PowerVoting &amp;mdash; a tool to compare the relative voting power of districts across the United States in federal elections (with Leyla Jacoby).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More skills</title>
      <link>https://miles.land/portfolio/more-skills/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2001 14:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miles.land/portfolio/more-skills/</guid>
      <description>Hackathons I love hackathons, whether it&amp;rsquo;s as a participant or—as of recently—a judge. It&amp;rsquo;s hard to replicate the thrill of building.
 HackNEHS 1st place (Fall 2017): won first place in HackNEHS, a &amp;lsquo;hackathon&amp;rsquo; for New England high schools. Blueprint (@ MIT) 2nd place (Winter 2018): won second place in Blueprint, a national annual hackathon hosted at the MIT Media Lab. Hack Exeter (Spring 2019): won the Developer&amp;rsquo;s Award at Hack Exeter, a hackathon hosted at Phillips Exeter Academy.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>